http://superior-mason.com/privacy-policy/

Terms of use & Privacy
Welcome to Superior-Mason.com (the “Site”). Please read the following Website Terms of Use Agreement (“Agreement”) before using the Site. By accessing and using the Site you agree to be bound by all the terms of use set forth in this Agreement, as it may be amended from time to time. Please print a copy of this Agreement for your records. If you do not agree with these Terms of Use your sole recourse is to leave the Site immediately.
Superior Mason Products takes the issue of privacy on the Internet very seriously. Please see our Privacy Policy.
Ownership
The Site is owned and operated by Latium USA Trading, Inc., doing business as Superior Mason Products. Any and all content, data, graphics, photographs, images, audio, video, software systems, processes, trademarks, trade names and all other information, including without limitation, the “look and feel” of the Site (collectively the “Contents”) contained in the Site are property to Latium, its affiliates and/or licensors. The Content is protected by United States and international copyright and trademark laws.
Use of contents
You may use the Site only for you or your entity’s internal general business purposes, such as gathering information for your personal purchase or collecting necessary information as a dealer of products provided by Superior Mason Products. The information provided in the Site is provided only in connection with the marketing efforts of Superior Mason Products and is not to be used to seek similar opportunities from suppliers in competition with Superior Mason Products. You may access or use the Site and its content only to process transactions and may not access or use the Site or its content to provide information to third parties unrelated to the allowed purposes of the Site. Content copied, downloaded or printed must retain all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices. For commercial use of any portion of the contents, you must secure the written consent from the appropriate content provider.
Use of site
Your use of the Site is at the sole discretion of Superior Mason Products, which may deny you further use of the Site at any time, for any reason, with or without cause. Your use of the Site and any orders for merchandise placed through this Site does not entitle you to continued use of the Site.
Your use of the Site must always comply with applicable law. In particular, but without limitation, you agree and represent not to use the Site to:
Impersonate any person or entity or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity;
Upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;
Upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party; or
Upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software, network, hardware or telecommunications equipment.
Product display
We have made every effort to display the products featured on the Site as accurately as possible. Please note, however, that the colors we use, as well as the display and color capabilities of your particular computer monitor, will greatly affect the colors actually seen on the screen. The Site cannot be responsible for the limitations of your monitor’s display of any color, texture, or detail of actual merchandise.
Registration and passwords
To access certain portions of the Site and/or to request brochures or specifications or obtain quotes you may be asked to complete an online registration form. In consideration of your use of the Site and the services provide on it, you agree to provide true, current, complete and accurate information as requested on any registration form to which the Site may direct you, and to update that registration information promptly in the event of change.
Upon registration, you will choose a username and password. You alone are responsible for keeping that password and username confidential and for any and all activity that occurs on the Site under such password or username. You agree to immediately notify Superior Mason Products of any unauthorized use of your password or username or any other breach of security.
User submissions
By voluntarily submitting information, communications or content (including pictures and anecdotes) to the Site, you agree that such submissions are non-confidential for all purposes. You further agree that such submissions become the property of Superior Mason Products and that all title and interest therein, including all rights of copyright, shall rest with Superior Mason Products at the time they are submitted and/or posted. Such submissions are subject to being used, reproduced, modified, published, edited, translated, distributed, performed and displayed in any media or medium, or any form, format or forum now known or hereafter developed, for any purpose, in perpetuity without further notice. The submission of such materials in no way creates any obligation or duty on the part of Superior Mason Products to post or use such materials or, if we do so, to give you credit.
Links to other sites
The Site may contain links to third party websites. Such third party websites are not under the control of Superior Mason Products. Please note that Superior Mason Products is not responsible for the accuracy or content of websites of other providers that may have links from the Site. Accordingly, Superior Mason Products can make no representation to you concerning the terms of use, privacy policies or content of these sites, nor can the fact that Superior Mason Products has provided this link serve as an endorsement by Superior Mason Products of this or any other site. In creating hypertext links to any other website, Superior Mason Products is not recommending that website or giving any assurances as to its standing. Superior Mason Products is providing this link only as a convenience to you. The inclusion of these links is not intended to reflect their importance, nor is it intended to endorse any views expressed, or products or services offered on those outside sites, or the organizations sponsoring those sites. Superior Mason Products makes no warranties, explicit or implied, regarding the performance of the links, the performance of the outside sites or the contents of the outside sites. If you decide to access linked third party websites, you do so at your own risk.
Indemnification
YOU AGREE TO DEFEND, INDEMNIFY AND HOLD COMPLETELY HARMLESS SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS AND ITS AFFILIATES FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, DAMAGES, COSTS, AND EXPENSES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION CLAIMS BASED UPON THE NEGLIGENCE OF SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS, ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THE MATERIALS IT CONTAINS, AND ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE.
Disclaimer of warranties
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT:
– YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, NON-INTERFERENCE WITH INFORMATION, AND ACCURACY OF INFORMATIONAL CONTENT. THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT INFORMATION PROVIDED HEREUNDER, OUR EFFORTS, OR THE SITE WILL FULFILL ANY OF YOUR PARTICULAR PURPOSES OR NEEDS.
SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTSMAKES NO WARRANTY THAT:
YOUR USE OF THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE;
THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; OR
THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
– ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.
– NO INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM Superior Mason Products OR THROUGH THIS SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED ON THIS AGREEMENT.
Contests
From time to time we may offer and/or co-sponsor contests or promotions on the Site. Each of the activities shall be governed by specific rules accessible from the pages of the Site offering the promotion or when you submit your entry.
Limitations and exclusions of liability
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), RESULTING FROM:
THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SITE;
UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA;
STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SITE; OR,
ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SITE.
IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE SITE, OR ANY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREON, OR REFUSE TO ABIDE BY THIS AGREEMENT, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE YOUR USE.
NOTWITHSTANING THE FOREGOING, SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS’S (AND ITS AFFILIATE’S, IF ANY) LIABILITY TO YOU SHALL BE LIMITED IN ALL INSTANCES TO THE SUM OF PAYMENTS MADE FOR MERCHANDISE PURCHASED THROUGH THIS SITE, BUT IN NO CASE SHALL SUCH AMOUNT EXCEED $1,000. YOU FURTHER AGREE NOT TO JOIN IN ANY LAWSUIT WITH ANOTHER PERSON OR SERVE AS A CLASS REPRESENTATIVE OF ANY CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT AGAINST SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SITE.
SUPERIOR MASON PRODUCTS SHALL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY REPRESENTATIONS ON THIRD PARTY SITES IN RELATION TO THE INFORMATION PROVIDED IN THIS SITE.
Modification
Superior Mason Products may update, revise, supplement, modify or amend this Agreement at any time. Any updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments shall be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. You agree that you will be bound by this Agreement, however and whenever it is updated, revised, supplemented, modified, or amended, whether you have actual or constructive notice of the updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments.
Entire Agreement
This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and Superior Mason Products with respect to your use of the Site. There are no other representations, warranties, terms, agreements or conditions, either written or oral, with respect to your use of the Site except as set forth in this Agreement.
Severability
If any provision of this Agreement is deemed unlawful, void, voidable or unenforceable for any reason, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this Agreement and shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any remaining provisions.
Governing law and venue
This Agreement, the entire relationship between you and Superior Mason Products, and any litigation or other legal proceeding between you and Superior Mason Products (whether grounded in tort, contract, law or equity) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without giving effect to its choice of law rules.
This contract is fully performable in Suffolk County, New York. Any litigation arising between the parties hereto shall be brought only in the state or federal courts having subject matter jurisdiction in Suffolk County, New York. You hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consent to the jurisdiction of any such courts and hereby irrevocably and unconditionally waive any defense of an inconvenient forum for the maintenance of any action or proceeding in any such court, any objection to venue with respect to any such action or proceeding, and any right of jurisdiction on account of the place of residence or domicile of any party hereto.
Termination
Superior Mason Products may terminate your right to use this Site, with or without cause at any time in its sole discretion, including, without limitation, your violation of this Agreement, failure to provide accurate registration data, and lack of use. In the event of termination, all representations, warranties, indemnifications, and promises made by you shall survive.
Cautionary Statement About Forward-Looking Statements
The Site may include forward-looking statements within the meaning of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. These statements related to analyses and other information that are based on management’s beliefs, certain assumptions made by management, forecasts of future results, and current expectations, estimates and projections about the markets and economy in which we and our various segments operate. The statements contained in this communication that are not statements of historical fact may include forward-looking statements that involve a number of risks and uncertainties.
We have used the words “anticipate,” “intend,” “may,” “expect,” “believe,” “should,” “plan,” “will,” “estimate,” and variations of such words and similar expressions in this communication to identify such forward-looking statement. These statements are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions, which are difficult to predict and many of which are beyond our control. Therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from those matters expressed or implied in such forward-looking statements. We undertake no obligation to update publicly any forward-looking statements, whether as a result of future events, new information or otherwise.
Contact Information
If you have a comment, question or request, or if you need to contact Superior Mason Products for any other reason, there are four easy ways to do so:
a. E-mail: You can e-mail us under the “Contact” section of the Site.
b. You may call us at 844-638-2572. If you call after normal business hours, please leave a message and your telephone number. We will get back to you as quickly as possible. Normal office hours are Monday through Friday, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. Eastern Time.
c. U.S. Mail: Send mail to us at:
Superior Mason Products
5005 Veterans Memorial Highway
Holbrook, NY 11741
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Superior-Mason.com, the website of Latium USA Trading, Inc., d/ b/a Superior Mason Products  (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”). Latium respects the privacy of its customers and users and has adopted this privacy policy to describe how we collect and use information on the Site and the choices available to you as to how your information is collected and used.
Information collected by the site
In connection with your use of the Site the following information is collected:
The domain name, but not the email address of visitors to our Site.
The email address of users who communicate with us via email.
Aggregate information on what pages on the Site users access or visit.
Information volunteered by the user, such as Site registration, email update requests and general requests for information.
Disclosure of information
By using the Site you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your personal information as described in this Policy.
We do not disclose any non-public personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law, however, we may choose to disclose collected information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other similar companies with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We may also share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties but such summary information will not identify any specifics related to you. We may use the personal identifying information you provide to administer Site usage and monitor traffic levels and to contact you regarding improvements to our Site and our services. We also may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Your email address will only be used to contact you directly regarding services, products or information that we believe might be of interest to you. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others.
Access to your non-public personal information is restricted to those employees who need to know that information to provide merchandise or information to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your non-public personal information.
Choice / Opt out
If you prefer that we not disclose non-public information about you to non affiliated third parties you may opt out of those disclosures by directing us not to make those disclosures by email or telephone call to 844-638-2572. If you receive communications from us that you do not want to receive, you can opt out from receiving those communications by specifically telling us to stop sending them to you.
Security
It should be noted that emails and other information you send to us is not encrypted and cannot be considered a secure means of transmitting sensitive information. We will never ask you to submit your financial data, such as your credit card account numbers, via email. Any such requests are likely to be a scam and should not be opened or responded to. You should be aware of the limitations of security, authentication, encryption and privacy measures used in connection with the internet and that any information you transmit through the Site may be damaged, corrupted, “sniffed” and/or accessed by another person without your permission. Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us “perfect security” does not exist on the internet. We cannot insure or warrant the ultimate security of any information you transmit.
Collection and use of IP addresses
We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as your ID that the Site uses to track the pages you have visited. We may use cookies to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We may use your ID to identify you anonymously in our data base and track information while you are on the Site. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the Site. However, if you turn off cookies then you may not be able to utilize certain features of the Site.
Linked sites
The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for content or the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal, identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site.
Children’s Privacy
The Site is not directed at children under the age of 18 and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If we are notified that such personal information has been obtained that information will be immediately and permanently deleted from our records.
Changes in Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy may be occasionally changed. If we do we will post the changes on the Site and the changes will take effect as soon as posted. Your use of the Site after such changes have been posted constitutes your agreement to those changes.
Contact Us
Full Name (required)
Email
Telephone
Message
